(shoes tapping)
What are you waiting for?
If you're gonna switch
then do it already.
Something wrong, brat?
The Innate Domain's closed off.
The special grade is dead.
Now we just need
Itadori to return safely.
Yeah, sorry but he isn't
going to be coming back.
There's no reason to be scared.
I'm in such a great
mood right now.
Let's just chat for a bit.
The kid had it coming
for just using me without
making any kind of a deal,
and now it feels like,
he's having some
trouble switching back
but then no matter what he did,
this would've ended up the same.
So I've been thinking
about the different ways,
I can do this.
(laughs)
What are you doing?
I'm taking this brat a hostage.
What do you mean?
It's simple.
See, I can live without this,
but that ain't true
for your punk friend.
Switching out with
me means he dies.
Oh, and also for good measure.
Sukuna's finger.
That special grade
cursed spirit in there,
must have swallowed it.
And with that, I'm
now is free as a bird,
and now you can be frightened
because I'm about to kill
you just for the hell of it.
And just like that, our
positions are now reversed.
(Opening Theme Music)
The only thing
granted equally to all,
is an unfair reality.
You don't get it, but I do.
Itadori is coming back,
even if that means he'll die,
that's just who he is.
You give him too much credit.
He's just a little tougher
and a whole lot denser
than other human beings are.
You should've seen
him a minute ago.
He was scared out of his
mind and about to lose it.
Prattling on about his
regrets and all that nonsense.
So it's obvious the guy
doesn't have the guts
to kill himself.
His left hand's been restored.
Healing.
He can use reverse
curse techniques
and Sukuna's incarnated.
So even though he
can live without a heart,
it should still be
damaging to him.
I'll make sure he heals that
heart before Itadori returns.
I just have to convince
him he can't beat me
without a heart in his body.
But can I do that?
I froze up when that
other special-grade
was in front of me.
It's not about
whether I can do it,
I have to do it.
Oh, it feels so good to
be back outside again.
Let's use all this open space.
(grunts)
How interesting.
You can use your Shikigami,
but you still come
at me yourself.
(grunts)
Give me more.
And more.
Put more curse behind it,
when you strike me.
(laughs)
Orochi.
Gang up on him now.
Now, what did I say?
Let's use the open space.
It's not even a
matter of jujutsu,
his power and his agility
are on a different level.
That's a nice technique there.
(grunts)
Now what?
I used up one of my Shikigami
to escape that Innate Domain.
Demon Dog White and
Orochi are both destroyed
and Nue's at his limit.
I should release him before
he gets destroyed too.
I get it now.
You use the shadows
to create your Shikigami.
It makes no difference
if he knows that now.
So what's it to you?
It's not a generic
technique that uses charms,
it's adaptable as well.
There's just one
thing I don't get.
Why did you run back then?
Kind of a waste of your talents.
Whatever.
Either way that certainly
won't be enough to fix this.
So he's figured it out.
Risking your life
for meaningless shit.
This punk isn't even close
to being worth the effort.
[Itadori] Why'd you
bother saving me then?
[Megumi] The only thing
granted equally to all,
is an unfair reality.
If I have the time
to curse someone,
I'd rather spend it
thinking about people I love.
[Megumi] There was
never any doubt as to
what a good person she was.
She deserved happiness
more than anyone ever did,
but Tsumiki was still cursed.
While the father
who named Megumi,
with no regard for my gender,
is still off somewhere
living as he pleases.
Karma isn't fully automatic.
Evil people are only
judged under the law.
Jujutsu sorcerers
are just another cog
in that machine of retribution.
I want good people
to enjoy fairness,
even if only a few will.
And so, I save people unequally.
That's the way.
So this is when you start
burning through your life.
Now I see.
Well, in that case,
Megumi, show me what you got.
Sacred treasure, swing and ring,
ring Eight Grip.
Oh and just so you know,
I didn't have any logical
reason for saving you back then.
Even though it was dangerous,
I just couldn't bear to see
a good person like you die.
Sure I had my reservations,
but ultimately I did it for
selfish emotional reasons,
but that's fine though.
I'm a jujutsu sorcerer.
I'm not a hero.
In all this time,
I've never once
regretted saving you.
Right,
you're really a pretty
smart guy Fushiguro.
I know you've put a
lot of thought into this.
I think your conviction
is a good one,
but I don't think mine
is exactly wrong either.
Sorry, I guess I'm done for.
At least I won't be here
worrying about you anymore,
or Kugisaki or Gojou.
I hope you live a long life.
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
Well, you're gonna tell me,
what possibly could
have been so important
that you decided to use a
precious finger on Sukuna?
Tried to see how strong he is?
Well, the test was half
baked, I'll admit that,
but we did still
learn a few things.
I can only pray
that's not an excuse.
(mumbles)
Stop talking already,
no one can understand you.
Yet the meaning flows
right into our minds.
It creeps me out.
Hello and welcome.
Would you like a
table for one, sir?
Yes, thank you.
One for lunch.
I told them that if
they encountered one,
their choices were
either run or die.
I specifically warned them
that fighting was
absolutely not an option.
It was intentional huh?
What do you mean by that?
The special grade
sending first years
to rescue five people
who may already be dead,
should have been
out of the question.
Besides with Yuuji,
I was the one who
forced the issue
and got the kid's execution
sentence suspended.
Some higher-ups
didn't like that,
and so they took
advantage of my absence
and used the special
grade to dispose of Yuuji.
If the other two
had died as well,
it'd mean more trouble for me,
and they would have killed
two birds with one stone.
Yeah, but wait, when the
initial dispatch went out,
no one knew it would
become a special grade.
Trying to pin the
blame is such a pain.
Maybe I ought to
just cut to the chase
and go kill off all
those higher-ups.
You're not usually
this emotional.
Good to see you, Miss Ieiri.
Sounds to me,
like you took quite
a liking to this one.
I've always been the kind of guy
who cares about his students.
Regardless, you shouldn't
torment Ijichi too much.
It's hard for him to be stuck
between us and the higher-ups.
Yes, I don't care about
another man's hardships.
Keep going, keep going.
Is that so?
So this here is
Sukuna's vessel huh?
I can cut him up, yes?
Just make good use of him.
Oh I will.
Who do you think I am?
He said live a long life?
Guess that doesn't mean
much when you die yourself.
First time having a
partner of yours die on you?
-One my age?
-Yeah.
You're taking it well though.
Yeah, you too.
Well, of course.
Two weeks ago, I
didn't even know him.
I'm not the type to break
down and fall to pieces,
when a guy I barely know dies.
I mean, jeez.
It's hot, huh?
Yeah, wonder if it's time
for summer uniforms.
So what's this?
You're looking even more
bummed-out than usual, Megumi.
Having a wake?
What's up Zenin?
Stop calling me by my last name.
Maki, Maki.
Hey I'm talking here, shut it.
Are you serious right now?
You don't know why
they're so down now?
No, should I?
Someone died yesterday, a boy.
He was one of the first years.
Bonito flakes.
Well, why didn't you say so?
Now I look like some
kind of heartless,
cold-blooded ice-demon
Yeah, that's how you came off.
Tuna and mayo.
-Don't say that.
-So who are these guys?
You're supposed to try
to make me feel better.
The second years.
You have to try to be
kinder to your underclassmen.
Hey, being soft on them
isn't gonna help them.
[Megumi] Zenin is the
best of all the students
at wielding curse tools.
Salmon roe.
[Megumi] And that's the
Cursed Speech user, Inumaki.
He can only speak in
ingredients of rice balls.
He is a little bit softer
whenever Yuuta's around though.
And that's Panda.
There's one more.
His name is Okkotsu,
and he's actually the only
second year I genuinely respect.
But he's overseas right now.
Panda?
That's all you're
giving me is Panda.
Sorry to hit you up with this
now when you're in mourning.
Bad timing.
Please forgive us for that.
But see, we'd like you both
to be in the Kyoto Sister
School Exchange Event.
Kyoto Sister School
Exchange Event?
What is that?
It's a get-together with the
other Tech school in Kyoto,
but isn't that event mainly
for second and
third year students?
Turns out the idiot third years
got themselves suspended,
so you need to participate.
So what exactly do
you do at this event?
Smash bros?
I rule at the Wii version.
I'll Meteor Smash your butts.
We'll make a three man team.
The whole event
starts with the principals
of the Tokyo and Kyoto schools.
Each principal proposes
a form of competition
that will be held
for an entire day,
over the course of two days.
At least that's how
it's supposed to go.
It goes like this.
Day one's team battles and
day two's individual battles.
Salmon.
Team battles and individual?
You mean we fight
other jujutsu sorcerers.
Yeah, they're jujutsu battles
where anything short
of killing is fair game.
Don't worry, we'll train you up.
So you probably
won't get killed.
Do we have enough
jujutsu sorcerers?
I thought we were really short.
Do you have the time?
Hey, good question.
For now we're good.
The dark emotions people harbor
from late winter through spring,
cause an outburst of
curses in early summer,
so that's our busy season.
Sometimes we're
busy all year long,
but things should be settling
down here soon enough.
Yeah?
So are you in?
I understand your
partner just died.
-We're in.
Cause I...
Have to get stronger
and I'll do anything
to achieve that.
But if I decide your training
exchange event is pointless,
I'll quit instantly.
Same here.
Well, people this corky,
are all the more
worthwhile to train.
Bonito flakes.
So you're saying that your boss,
wants to reverse the
current relative positions
of humans and curses.
Is that right?
Yeah, that's pretty close,
but it's slightly different.
Humans are
practically made of lies,
for every positive action
and emotion they show,
there's always a flip side,
and yet negative emotions like
hatred and hostility are
truths without falsehood.
Since we curses are born
from those raw true emotions,
that makes us true pure beings.
Imitation should be eliminated.
Yet at the moment,
you're the ones who
are getting eliminated.
And that's why we've
come here to ask you,
what can we do to defeat
the jujutsu sorcerers?
If you want to win, you'll
need to fulfill two conditions.
Good, what are these conditions?
The first thing, concerns
the strongest sorcerer.
You must somehow render
Satoru Gojou incapable of fighting.
The second, is to
get Ryoumen Sukuna
and Yuuji Itadori on your side.
But hold on a minute,
he died, didn't he?
Wait, that Yuuji
Itadori, he's dead.
Yeah?
Did he die?
I'm not so sure.
Don't poke around inside me
without my permission, punk-ass.
(Closing Theme Music)
[Both] Juju Stroll.
[Toge] Salmon.
[Maki] You stink.
[Panda] I don't stink.
I do not stink.
Why you be so mean?
You're treating
you like an animal.
Because you're a Panda.
Mustard leaf.
And you smell like an animal.
I keep telling you to
take a bath, but you don't.
I don't mind getting all wet.
Unlike you humans all us
panda bears don't sweat,
but I Febreze every day.
So I know I don't stick.
Here's your first task,
step up and take a whiff.
(sniffing)
He doesn't really stink.
Actually, Panda sort
of smells like the sun.
-Sunshine.
(upbeat music)